Live as one. Die as one.
The Sacrament is a horror, thriller film directed by Ti West.
Two journalists set out to document their friend's
journey to reunite with his estranged sister.
They track her to an undisclosed location where they are welcomed into the remote world of "Eden Parish," a self-sustained rural utopia composed of nearly two hundred
members and overseen by a mysterious leader known only as "Father." It quickly becomes evident to the newcomers that this paradise may not be as it seems.
Eden Parish harbors a twisted secret.
What started as just another documentary shoot
soon becomes a fight for survival.
Jake, played by Joe Swanberg.
Sam Turner, played by AJ Bowen.
Patrick Carter, played by Kentucker Audley.
Father, played by Gene Jones.
Caroline, played by Amy Seimetz.
Mindy, played by Kate Forbes.
The Sacrament is a 2013 American found footage horror
film written and directed by Ti West.
Bowen and Joe Swanberg play VICE journalists who document their co-worker's (Kentucker Audley)
attempt to locate his sister (Amy Seimetz) after she joins a reclusive religious commune.
The film's plot is inspired by the real-life events
of the Jonestown Massacre of 1978.
The film explores themes of journalist, poison,
lethal injection, interview, cult.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.